Guide to the Stanford University, Memorial Church, Records SC0290
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Materials, Accession ARCH-2015-109
  - Memorial service records, 1973-2000 (Box 1)
- Additional Materials, Accession-ARCH-2016-008
  - Robert Hamerton-Kelly clippings and photographs, 1972-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Robert Hamerton-Kelly, Educational Provocateur: A Tenth Anniversary Tribute at the Stanford University Faculty Club," by Gail Stockholm, circa 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Additional Materials: Window Restoration Rubbings, Accession ARCH-2017-228
  - Flight into Egypt, 2012; 14A (Box 1)
  - Flight into Egypt, 2012 May; 14B (Box 1)
  - Flight into Egypt, 2013; 14C (Box 1)
  - Flight into Egypt, 2013; 14D (Box 1)
  - Annunciation, 2013; 13A (Box 2)
  - Annunciation, 2014; 13B (Box 2)
  - Annunciation, 2014; 13C (Box 2)
  - Annunciation, 2014; 13D (Box 2)
  - Annunciation, 2014; 13E (Box 2)
  - Window 10, 2000 Dec 29; 10-1 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2000 Dec 28; 10-1-2 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 20; 10-2-1 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 24; 10-2-2-1 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 24; 10-2-2-2 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 22; 10-2-3 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 5; 10-3-1 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 8; 10-3-2 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 23; 10-5 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 22; 10-5-2 (Box 3)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 22; 10-5-1 (Box 4)
  - Window 10, 2000 Nov 29; 10-4-1 (Box 4)
  - Window 10, 2000 Nov 29; 10-4-2 (Box 4)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 8; 10-3-3 (Box 4)
  - Window 10, 2001 Jan 8; 10-3-2 (Box 4)
  - Holy Family, 15A (Box 5)
  - Holy Family, 15B (Box 5)
  - Holy Family, 15C (Box 5)
  - Holy Family, 15D (Box 5)
  - Holy Family, 15E (Box 5)